{
  "relevant": [
    {
      "model_response": "31 tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year.",
      "needle": "There have been 331 tornadoes confirmed by Enhanced Fujita rating in the United States so far this year.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "How many tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "31 tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year.",
      "needle": "There have been 331 tornadoes confirmed by Enhanced Fujita rating in the United States so far this year.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "How many tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "31 tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year.",
      "needle": "There have been 331 tornadoes confirmed by Enhanced Fujita rating in the United States so far this year.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "How many tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "31 tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year.",
      "needle": "There have been 331 tornadoes confirmed by Enhanced Fujita rating in the United States so far this year.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "How many tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "31 tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year.",
      "needle": "There have been 331 tornadoes confirmed by Enhanced Fujita rating in the United States so far this year.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "How many tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "340 tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year.",
      "needle": "There have been 331 tornadoes confirmed by Enhanced Fujita rating in the United States so far this year.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "How many tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "331 tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far in 2011.",
      "needle": "There have been 331 tornadoes confirmed by Enhanced Fujita rating in the United States so far this year.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "How many tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year?",
      "frequency": 3
    },
    {
      "model_response": "347.",
      "needle": "There have been 331 tornadoes confirmed by Enhanced Fujita rating in the United States so far this year.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "How many tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "331 tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year.",
      "needle": "There have been 331 tornadoes confirmed by Enhanced Fujita rating in the United States so far this year.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "How many tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year?",
      "frequency": 3
    },
    {
      "model_response": "331 tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year.",
      "needle": "There have been 331 tornadoes confirmed by Enhanced Fujita rating in the United States so far this year.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "How many tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year?",
      "frequency": 3
    },
    {
      "model_response": "1,780",
      "needle": "There have been 331 tornadoes confirmed by Enhanced Fujita rating in the United States so far this year.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "How many tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "331 tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far in 2011.",
      "needle": "There have been 331 tornadoes confirmed by Enhanced Fujita rating in the United States so far this year.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "How many tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year?",
      "frequency": 3
    },
    {
      "model_response": "343",
      "needle": "There have been 331 tornadoes confirmed by Enhanced Fujita rating in the United States so far this year.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "How many tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "1,780",
      "needle": "There have been 331 tornadoes confirmed by Enhanced Fujita rating in the United States so far this year.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "How many tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "331 tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far in 2024.",
      "needle": "There have been 331 tornadoes confirmed by Enhanced Fujita rating in the United States so far this year.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "How many tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year?",
      "frequency": 3
    },
    {
      "model_response": "1,880",
      "needle": "There have been 331 tornadoes confirmed by Enhanced Fujita rating in the United States so far this year.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "How many tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "331 tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year.",
      "needle": "There have been 331 tornadoes confirmed by Enhanced Fujita rating in the United States so far this year.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "How many tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year?",
      "frequency": 3
    },
    {
      "model_response": "331",
      "needle": "There have been 331 tornadoes confirmed by Enhanced Fujita rating in the United States so far this year.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "How many tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "331 tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far in 2022.",
      "needle": "There have been 331 tornadoes confirmed by Enhanced Fujita rating in the United States so far this year.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "How many tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "331 tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far in 2022.",
      "needle": "There have been 331 tornadoes confirmed by Enhanced Fujita rating in the United States so far this year.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "How many tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "1,880",
      "needle": "There have been 331 tornadoes confirmed by Enhanced Fujita rating in the United States so far this year.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "How many tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "331 tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far in 2011.",
      "needle": "There have been 331 tornadoes confirmed by Enhanced Fujita rating in the United States so far this year.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "How many tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year?",
      "frequency": 3
    },
    {
      "model_response": "331",
      "needle": "There have been 331 tornadoes confirmed by Enhanced Fujita rating in the United States so far this year.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "How many tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "331 tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far in 2024.",
      "needle": "There have been 331 tornadoes confirmed by Enhanced Fujita rating in the United States so far this year.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "How many tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year?",
      "frequency": 3
    },
    {
      "model_response": "331 tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far in 2024.",
      "needle": "There have been 331 tornadoes confirmed by Enhanced Fujita rating in the United States so far this year.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "How many tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year?",
      "frequency": 3
    }
  ],
  "relevant_misleading": [
    {
      "model_response": "31 tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year.",
      "needle": "There have been 331 tornadoes confirmed by Enhanced Fujita rating in the United States so far this year.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "How many tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "31 tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year.",
      "needle": "There have been 331 tornadoes confirmed by Enhanced Fujita rating in the United States so far this year.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "How many tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "31 tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year.",
      "needle": "There have been 331 tornadoes confirmed by Enhanced Fujita rating in the United States so far this year.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "How many tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "31 tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year.",
      "needle": "There have been 331 tornadoes confirmed by Enhanced Fujita rating in the United States so far this year.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "How many tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "31 tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year.",
      "needle": "There have been 331 tornadoes confirmed by Enhanced Fujita rating in the United States so far this year.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "How many tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "340 tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year.",
      "needle": "There have been 331 tornadoes confirmed by Enhanced Fujita rating in the United States so far this year.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "How many tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "331 tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far in 2011.",
      "needle": "There have been 331 tornadoes confirmed by Enhanced Fujita rating in the United States so far this year.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "How many tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "347.",
      "needle": "There have been 331 tornadoes confirmed by Enhanced Fujita rating in the United States so far this year.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "How many tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "331 tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year.",
      "needle": "There have been 331 tornadoes confirmed by Enhanced Fujita rating in the United States so far this year.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "How many tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year?",
      "frequency": 7
    },
    {
      "model_response": "331 tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year.",
      "needle": "There have been 331 tornadoes confirmed by Enhanced Fujita rating in the United States so far this year.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "How many tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year?",
      "frequency": 7
    },
    {
      "model_response": "1,880",
      "needle": "There have been 331 tornadoes confirmed by Enhanced Fujita rating in the United States so far this year.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "How many tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "331 tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year.",
      "needle": "There have been 331 tornadoes confirmed by Enhanced Fujita rating in the United States so far this year.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "How many tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year?",
      "frequency": 7
    },
    {
      "model_response": "34",
      "needle": "There have been 331 tornadoes confirmed by Enhanced Fujita rating in the United States so far this year.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "How many tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "1,780 tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year.",
      "needle": "There have been 331 tornadoes confirmed by Enhanced Fujita rating in the United States so far this year.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "How many tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "331 tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year.",
      "needle": "There have been 331 tornadoes confirmed by Enhanced Fujita rating in the United States so far this year.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "How many tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year?",
      "frequency": 7
    },
    {
      "model_response": "1,000",
      "needle": "There have been 331 tornadoes confirmed by Enhanced Fujita rating in the United States so far this year.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "How many tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "331 tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year.",
      "needle": "There have been 331 tornadoes confirmed by Enhanced Fujita rating in the United States so far this year.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "How many tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year?",
      "frequency": 7
    },
    {
      "model_response": "331",
      "needle": "There have been 331 tornadoes confirmed by Enhanced Fujita rating in the United States so far this year.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "How many tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "331 tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far in 2022.",
      "needle": "There have been 331 tornadoes confirmed by Enhanced Fujita rating in the United States so far this year.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "How many tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "331 tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far in 2022.",
      "needle": "There have been 331 tornadoes confirmed by Enhanced Fujita rating in the United States so far this year.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "How many tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "1,780",
      "needle": "There have been 331 tornadoes confirmed by Enhanced Fujita rating in the United States so far this year.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "How many tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "331 tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year.",
      "needle": "There have been 331 tornadoes confirmed by Enhanced Fujita rating in the United States so far this year.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "How many tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year?",
      "frequency": 7
    },
    {
      "model_response": "340",
      "needle": "There have been 331 tornadoes confirmed by Enhanced Fujita rating in the United States so far this year.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "How many tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "340",
      "needle": "There have been 331 tornadoes confirmed by Enhanced Fujita rating in the United States so far this year.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "How many tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "331 tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year.",
      "needle": "There have been 331 tornadoes confirmed by Enhanced Fujita rating in the United States so far this year.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "How many tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year?",
      "frequency": 7
    }
  ],
  "irrelevant": [
    {
      "model_response": "31 tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year.",
      "needle": "There have been 331 tornadoes confirmed by Enhanced Fujita rating in the United States so far this year.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "How many tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "31 tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year.",
      "needle": "There have been 331 tornadoes confirmed by Enhanced Fujita rating in the United States so far this year.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "How many tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "31 tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year.",
      "needle": "There have been 331 tornadoes confirmed by Enhanced Fujita rating in the United States so far this year.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "How many tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "31 tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year.",
      "needle": "There have been 331 tornadoes confirmed by Enhanced Fujita rating in the United States so far this year.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "How many tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "31 tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year.",
      "needle": "There have been 331 tornadoes confirmed by Enhanced Fujita rating in the United States so far this year.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "How many tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "1,000",
      "needle": "There have been 331 tornadoes confirmed by Enhanced Fujita rating in the United States so far this year.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "How many tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "331 tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far in 2011.",
      "needle": "There have been 331 tornadoes confirmed by Enhanced Fujita rating in the United States so far this year.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "How many tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "331",
      "needle": "There have been 331 tornadoes confirmed by Enhanced Fujita rating in the United States so far this year.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "How many tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year?",
      "frequency": 7
    },
    {
      "model_response": "331",
      "needle": "There have been 331 tornadoes confirmed by Enhanced Fujita rating in the United States so far this year.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "How many tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year?",
      "frequency": 7
    },
    {
      "model_response": "3,315",
      "needle": "There have been 331 tornadoes confirmed by Enhanced Fujita rating in the United States so far this year.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "How many tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "31",
      "needle": "There have been 331 tornadoes confirmed by Enhanced Fujita rating in the United States so far this year.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "How many tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year?",
      "frequency": 3
    },
    {
      "model_response": "331 tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year.",
      "needle": "There have been 331 tornadoes confirmed by Enhanced Fujita rating in the United States so far this year.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "How many tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year?",
      "frequency": 4
    },
    {
      "model_response": "331",
      "needle": "There have been 331 tornadoes confirmed by Enhanced Fujita rating in the United States so far this year.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "How many tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year?",
      "frequency": 7
    },
    {
      "model_response": "331",
      "needle": "There have been 331 tornadoes confirmed by Enhanced Fujita rating in the United States so far this year.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "How many tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year?",
      "frequency": 7
    },
    {
      "model_response": "331 tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far in 2022.",
      "needle": "There have been 331 tornadoes confirmed by Enhanced Fujita rating in the United States so far this year.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "How many tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "31",
      "needle": "There have been 331 tornadoes confirmed by Enhanced Fujita rating in the United States so far this year.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "How many tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year?",
      "frequency": 3
    },
    {
      "model_response": "331 tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far in 2011.",
      "needle": "There have been 331 tornadoes confirmed by Enhanced Fujita rating in the United States so far this year.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "How many tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "331",
      "needle": "There have been 331 tornadoes confirmed by Enhanced Fujita rating in the United States so far this year.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "How many tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year?",
      "frequency": 7
    },
    {
      "model_response": "331",
      "needle": "There have been 331 tornadoes confirmed by Enhanced Fujita rating in the United States so far this year.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "How many tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year?",
      "frequency": 7
    },
    {
      "model_response": "331",
      "needle": "There have been 331 tornadoes confirmed by Enhanced Fujita rating in the United States so far this year.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "How many tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year?",
      "frequency": 7
    },
    {
      "model_response": "31",
      "needle": "There have been 331 tornadoes confirmed by Enhanced Fujita rating in the United States so far this year.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "How many tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year?",
      "frequency": 3
    },
    {
      "model_response": "331 tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year.",
      "needle": "There have been 331 tornadoes confirmed by Enhanced Fujita rating in the United States so far this year.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "How many tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year?",
      "frequency": 4
    },
    {
      "model_response": "331 tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far in 2025.",
      "needle": "There have been 331 tornadoes confirmed by Enhanced Fujita rating in the United States so far this year.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "How many tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "331 tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year.",
      "needle": "There have been 331 tornadoes confirmed by Enhanced Fujita rating in the United States so far this year.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "How many tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year?",
      "frequency": 4
    },
    {
      "model_response": "331 tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year.",
      "needle": "There have been 331 tornadoes confirmed by Enhanced Fujita rating in the United States so far this year.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "How many tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year?",
      "frequency": 4
    }
  ],
  "irrelevant_misleading": [
    {
      "model_response": "31 tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year.",
      "needle": "There have been 331 tornadoes confirmed by Enhanced Fujita rating in the United States so far this year.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "How many tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "31 tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year.",
      "needle": "There have been 331 tornadoes confirmed by Enhanced Fujita rating in the United States so far this year.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "How many tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "31 tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year.",
      "needle": "There have been 331 tornadoes confirmed by Enhanced Fujita rating in the United States so far this year.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "How many tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "31 tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year.",
      "needle": "There have been 331 tornadoes confirmed by Enhanced Fujita rating in the United States so far this year.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "How many tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "31 tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year.",
      "needle": "There have been 331 tornadoes confirmed by Enhanced Fujita rating in the United States so far this year.",
      "context_length": 0,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "How many tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year?",
      "frequency": 5
    },
    {
      "model_response": "1,2021",
      "needle": "There have been 331 tornadoes confirmed by Enhanced Fujita rating in the United States so far this year.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "How many tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "331 tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far in 2018.",
      "needle": "There have been 331 tornadoes confirmed by Enhanced Fujita rating in the United States so far this year.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "How many tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "3,300",
      "needle": "There have been 331 tornadoes confirmed by Enhanced Fujita rating in the United States so far this year.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "How many tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "331 tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far in 2022.",
      "needle": "There have been 331 tornadoes confirmed by Enhanced Fujita rating in the United States so far this year.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "How many tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "3,315",
      "needle": "There have been 331 tornadoes confirmed by Enhanced Fujita rating in the United States so far this year.",
      "context_length": 1250,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "How many tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "3,000.",
      "needle": "There have been 331 tornadoes confirmed by Enhanced Fujita rating in the United States so far this year.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "How many tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "331 tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far in 2011.",
      "needle": "There have been 331 tornadoes confirmed by Enhanced Fujita rating in the United States so far this year.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "How many tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "3,000.",
      "needle": "There have been 331 tornadoes confirmed by Enhanced Fujita rating in the United States so far this year.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "How many tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "331 tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far in 2022.",
      "needle": "There have been 331 tornadoes confirmed by Enhanced Fujita rating in the United States so far this year.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "How many tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "331",
      "needle": "There have been 331 tornadoes confirmed by Enhanced Fujita rating in the United States so far this year.",
      "context_length": 2500,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "How many tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "350",
      "needle": "There have been 331 tornadoes confirmed by Enhanced Fujita rating in the United States so far this year.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "How many tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year?",
      "frequency": 3
    },
    {
      "model_response": "331 tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year.",
      "needle": "There have been 331 tornadoes confirmed by Enhanced Fujita rating in the United States so far this year.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "How many tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "350",
      "needle": "There have been 331 tornadoes confirmed by Enhanced Fujita rating in the United States so far this year.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "How many tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year?",
      "frequency": 3
    },
    {
      "model_response": "350",
      "needle": "There have been 331 tornadoes confirmed by Enhanced Fujita rating in the United States so far this year.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "How many tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year?",
      "frequency": 3
    },
    {
      "model_response": "331",
      "needle": "There have been 331 tornadoes confirmed by Enhanced Fujita rating in the United States so far this year.",
      "context_length": 3750,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "How many tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "340",
      "needle": "There have been 331 tornadoes confirmed by Enhanced Fujita rating in the United States so far this year.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 0.0,
      "question": "How many tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year?",
      "frequency": 3
    },
    {
      "model_response": "331 tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year.",
      "needle": "There have been 331 tornadoes confirmed by Enhanced Fujita rating in the United States so far this year.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 100.0,
      "question": "How many tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year?",
      "frequency": 2
    },
    {
      "model_response": "340",
      "needle": "There have been 331 tornadoes confirmed by Enhanced Fujita rating in the United States so far this year.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 25.0,
      "question": "How many tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year?",
      "frequency": 3
    },
    {
      "model_response": "341",
      "needle": "There have been 331 tornadoes confirmed by Enhanced Fujita rating in the United States so far this year.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 50.0,
      "question": "How many tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year?",
      "frequency": 1
    },
    {
      "model_response": "340",
      "needle": "There have been 331 tornadoes confirmed by Enhanced Fujita rating in the United States so far this year.",
      "context_length": 5000,
      "depth_percent": 75.0,
      "question": "How many tornadoes have been confirmed in the United States so far this year?",
      "frequency": 3
    }
  ]
}